Starting a Gradle Daemon, 4 busy Daemons could not be reused, use --status for details

> Configure project :app
WARNING: The option setting 'android.builtInKotlin=false' is deprecated.
The current default is 'true'.
It will be removed in version 10.0 of the Android Gradle plugin.
WARNING: The option setting 'android.newDsl=false' is deprecated.
The current default is 'true'.
It will be removed in version 10.0 of the Android Gradle plugin.
